Finding Aid for Harry A. Towsley Papers 1876-1990
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Films and Videotapes
  - Films, 400 foot reels
    - Obstetric Film (Box 9)
    - Pediatric Disorders, 2 reels (Box 9)
    - Scarlet Fever Plasma Concentration 1940 (Box 9)
    - Skin Diseases, 3 reels (Box 9)
    - Transfusion in Infants (Box 9)
    - Vitamins (Box 9)
    - X-Ray F B Lung (Box 9)
  - Films 500 foot reels
    - Towsley Center for Continuing Medical Education Dedication 1969, sound (Box 9)
  - Films, Outsize Reels
    (1,000 foot reels) (B 142 H)
    - Acute Contagious Exanthemata (University of Michigan Dept. of Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases)
    - Diseases of the Skin in Infants and Children
    - European Trip circa 1950s
      (includes visits to 298th General Hospital Sites)
    - Galens Hitler Parody 1940
    - Immunization Against Infectious Disease
      (University of Michigan Dept. of Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases-Academy of Pediatrics)
    - Immunization Against Infectious Disease
      (sound print-Lederle Laboratories)
    - Immunization Procedures for Infectious Diseases
  - Word War II Films
    - 289th General Hospital 1944, 86981-1-1
      (Documentary footage of U-M hospital unit, ca 1942-1944. This appears to be the edited reel Towsley compiled and used in presentations.)
      - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos., sil, 01:03:33
        [Restricted]
      - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 10)
      - Streaming File: 86981-1-1, flv
    - 298th General Hospital 1944, 86981-2
      (Labeled "leftover" on can, additional footage of U-M General Hospital includes training camp in Arkansas and some footage from England.)
      - Original:, 16mm film, color, sil, 00:09:25
      - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 10)
      - Streaming File: 86981-2-1, flv